directoryofschools.com 2018-05-26

# Privacy Policy | Directory of Schools

This privacy statement covers the website Directoryofschools.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this notice, you should first contact us by email at privacy@Directoryofschools.com or by postal at: Directory of Schools LLC, 73 St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403.

This privacy statement covers the website Directoryofschools.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this notice, you should first contact us by email at privacy@Directoryofschools.com or by postal at: Directory of Schools LLC, 73 St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403.

Directoryofschools.com is a media property owned by Directory of Schools, LLC, a leading online marketing company. Directory of Schools, LLC, ("We," "Us," "Our," "Directoryofschools.com"), understands how important privacy is to Our members ("you," "your"). We have created this online Privacy Policy to let you know what information is being collected on Our websites, how the information is being used and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of the information. Please take a moment to review this policy and feel free to contact Us with any questions at privacy@Directoryofschools.com.

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?**

Generally, We gather two types of information. The first type of information is the Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Information") that you expressly provide when you enroll via the online registration forms on Our website or via telephone or chat conversations with Us. This Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, mailing address, email address, date of birth, gender and telephone. In addition to the Personal Information you provide to Us, We will also collect certain information online and offline arising out of your use of Directoryofschools.com, including but not limited to the number and type of offers you have responded to and completed.

This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website. ClickTale does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service. We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to convert and identify site issues.  
You can choose to disable the Service at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>

**CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California residents who disclose Personal Information to third-parties for marketing purposes are entitled to either

(1) a list detailing the categories of Personal Information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or

(2) a mechanism by which they may opt-out of having their Personal Information shared with third-parties. We have elected the second option and you may request that your Personal Information not be shared with third-parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: Directory of Schools LLC, 73, St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED?**

The non-personally identifiable information that We collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If you elect to provide Us with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Us and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other sales and marketing efforts.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We partner with other third parties to provide specific services (e.g., student loans, text books, and other education-related products and services). When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. Service provider forms may ask for contact information (such as name, email, address) and sensitive information (such as date of birth and social security number) for in order to perform their service (such as to verify previous student loans). These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**WHAT IS THE UNSUBSCRIBE PROCESS?**

Directoryofschools.com Offers:

We use your email address to notify you of program updates, special offers and promotions. You may select at any time to opt-out of receiving emailed marketing offers from Us, Our partners and/or Our affiliated companies using the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom any future email you receive from Us.

Non-affiliated 3rd Parties:

If you prefer not to receive email offers from Our non-affiliated third-parties, you may click the "Unsubscribe" link available on the bottom of each email you receive from a non-affiliated third-party, and follow the instructions on the screen.

Please note that suppressed contact information will not be used for any other purpose other than to ensure compliance with your opt-out request, in response to inquiries by law enforcement and to comply with any other applicable state and/or federal laws regarding your choices for commercial email marketing, such as the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM).

**WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW DO WE USE THEM?**

Directoryofschools.com uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to help save and retrieve passwords used on Directoryofschools.com and to save information on past activities and other preferences. That way, you don't have to re-enter information every time you visit Directoryofschools.com.

When you visit Directoryofschools.com, we read the cookie to help target and personalize offers to you. For example, the cookie can help ensure that you don't see an offer that you have already completed. Cookies also let Directoryofschools.com know if We have repeat visitors.

We also use cookies to identify which sites 0ur repeat visitors are coming from. Directoryofschools.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. Directoryofschools.com respects your privacy and Directoryofschools.com cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Directoryofschools.com works with third-parties to serve ads on Our websites. These ads may contain cookies and/or action tags (also known as single pixel gifs) to measure advertising effectiveness and gather completely anonymous information. We have no access to or control over these cookies or action tags.

You are always free to decline these cookies if your browser permits, however, you may not be able to use certain features on Directoryofschools.com and you may be asked to re-enter your password more frequently during your session.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Directoryofschools.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and offline.

DO THESE SAME PRIVACY POLICIES APPLY TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES THAT YOU ACCESS THROUGH DIRECTORYOFSCHOOLS.COM?

No. The Privacy Policy appearing on Directoryofschools.com relates only to Directoryofschools.com. You will notice that Our website may contain links to other sites, such as Our partners. We cannot be responsible for the privacy and security practices of other websites that you may access through Directoryofschools.com, even if displayed within a frame on Our site. You should always review a particular site's privacy and security policies when linking to that site before revealing any personal information to that site.

PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to obtain changes to this Privacy Policy electronically by visiting this Site. We require you to check back from time to time to review changes to Our Privacy Policy.

**TRANSFERABILITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

In the event We go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of Our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by means of notice on [Our Sites] for thirty (30) days prior to any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Information. For more information, please refer to the section labeled "Privacy Policy Changes," above.

**A SPECIAL NOTE REGARDING PEOPLE UNDER THE AGE OF 18 YEARS OLD**

Consumers under the age of 18 must not send any personal information to Us-including but not limited to their name, address or email address. Further, We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information from any individual under the age of 13. Our intention is to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). If a parent or guardian has knowledge or is made aware a child under the age of 13 has provided Us with Personal Information through Our site, Contact Us and We will delete the information about the child from Our database.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about the practices of the Directoryofschools.com you can contact Us by visiting the Contact Us section of this website, or via postal mail at: Directory of Schools LLC, 73, St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE (PRIVACY POLIC1INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES0. YOU AGREE THAT THE OUR LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY US TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.This privacy statement covers the website Directoryofschools.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this notice, you should first contact us by email at privacy@Directoryofschools.com or by postal at: Directory of Schools LLC, 73 St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403.

Directoryofschools.com is a media property owned by Directory of Schools, LLC, a leading online marketing company. Directory of Schools, LLC, ("We," "Us," "Our," "Directoryofschools.com"), understands how important privacy is to Our members ("you," "your"). We have created this online Privacy Policy to let you know what information is being collected on Our websites, how the information is being used and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of the information. Please take a moment to review this policy and feel free to contact Us with any questions at privacy@Directoryofschools.com.

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?**

Generally, We gather two types of information. The first type of information is the Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Information") that you expressly provide when you enroll via the online registration forms on Our website or via telephone or chat conversations wivth Us. This Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, mailing address, email address, date of birth, gender and telephone. In addition to the Personal Information you provide to Us, We will also collect certain information online and offline arising out of your use of Directoryofschools.com, including but not limited to the number and type of offers you have responded to and completed.

**CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California residents who disclose Personal Information to third-parties for marketing purposes are entitled to either

(1) a list detailing the categories of Personal Information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or

(2) a mechanism by which they may opt-out of having their Personal Information shared with third-parties. We have elected the second option and you may request that your Personal Information not be shared with third-parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: Directory of Schools LLC, 73, St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED?**

The non-personally identifiable information that We collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If you elect to provide Us with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Us and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other sales and marketing efforts.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We partner with other third parties to provide specific services (e.g., student loans, text books, and other education-related products and services). When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. Service provider forms may ask for contact information (such as name, email, address) and sensitive information (such as date of birth and social security number) for in order to perform their service (such as to verify previous student loans). These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**WHAT IS THE UNSUBSCRIBE PROCESS?**

**Directoryofschools.com Offers:**

We use your email address to notify you of program updates, special offers and promotions. You may select at any time to opt-out of receiving emailed marketing offers from Us, Our partners and/or Our affiliated companies using the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom any future email you receive from Us.

**Non-affiliated 3rd Parties:**

If you prefer not to receive email offers from Our non-affiliated third-parties, you may click the "Unsubscribe" link available on the bottom of each email you receive from a non-affiliated third-party, and follow the instructions on the screen.

Please note that suppressed contact information will not be used for any other purpose other than to ensure compliance with your opt-out request, in response to inquiries by law enforcement and to comply with any other applicable state and/or federal laws regarding your choices for commercial email marketing, such as the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM).

**WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW DO WE USE THEM?**

Directoryofschools.com uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to help save and retrieve passwords used on Directoryofschools.com and to save information on past activities and other preferences. That way, you don't have to re-enter information every time you visit Directoryofschools.com.

When you visit Directoryofschools.com, we read the cookie to help target and personalize offers to you. For example, the cookie can help ensure that you don't see an offer that you have already completed. Cookies also let Directoryofschools.com know if We have repeat visitors.

We also use cookies to identify which sites 0ur repeat visitors are coming from. Directoryofschools.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. Directoryofschools.com respects your privacy and Directoryofschools.com cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Directoryofschools.com works with third-parties to serve ads on Our websites. These ads may contain cookies and/or action tags (also known as single pixel gifs) to measure advertising effectiveness and gather completely anonymous information. We have no access to or control over these cookies or action tags.

You are always free to decline these cookies if your browser permits, however, you may not be able to use certain features on Directoryofschools.com and you may be asked to re-enter your password more frequently during your session.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Directoryofschools.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and offline. DO THESE SAME PRIVACY POLICIES APPLY TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES THAT YOU ACCESS THROUGH DIRECTORYOFSCHOOLS.COM?

No. The Privacy Policy appearing on Directoryofschools.com relates only to Directoryofschools.com. You will notice that Our website may contain links to other sites, such as Our partners. We cannot be responsible for the privacy and security practices of other websites that you may access through Directoryofschools.com, even if displayed within a frame on Our site. You should always review a particular site's privacy and security policies when linking to that site before revealing any personal information to that site.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to obtain changes to this Privacy Policy electronically by visiting this Site. We require you to check back from time to time to review changes to Our Privacy Policy.

**TRANSFERABILITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

In the event We go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of Our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by means of notice on [Our Sites] for thirty (30) days prior to any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Information. For more information, please refer to the section labeled "Privacy Policy Changes," above.

**A SPECIAL NOTE REGARDING PEOPLE UNDER THE AGE OF 18 YEARS OLD**

Consumers under the age of 18 must not send any personal information to Us-including but not limited to their name, address or email address. Further, We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information from any individual under the age of 13. Our intention is to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). If a parent or guardian has knowledge or is made aware a child under the age of 13 has provided Us with Personal Information through Our site, Contact Us and We will delete the information about the child from Our database.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about the practices of the Directoryofschools.com you can contact Us by visiting the Contact Us section of this website, or via postal mail at: Directory of Schools LLC, 73, St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE (PRIVACY POLIC1INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES0. YOU AGREE THAT THE OUR LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY US TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.Directoryofschools.com is a media property owned by Directory of Schools, LLC, a leading online marketing company. Directory of Schools, LLC, ("We," "Us," "Our," "Directoryofschools.com"), understands how important privacy is to Our members ("you," "your"). We have created this online Privacy Policy to let you know what information is being collected on Our websites, how the information is being used and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of the information. Please take a moment to review this policy and feel free to contact Us with any questions at privacy@Directoryofschools.com.

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?**

Generally, We gather two types of information. The first type of information is the Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Information") that you expressly provide when you enroll via the online registration forms on Our website or via telephone or chat conversations with Us. This Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, mailing address, email address, date of birth, gender and telephone. In addition to the Personal Information you provide to Us, We will also collect certain information online and offline arising out of your use of Directoryofschools.com, including but not limited to the number and type of offers you have responded to and completed.

**CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California residents who disclose Personal Information to third-parties for marketing purposes are entitled to either

(1) a list detailing the categories of Personal Information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or

(2) a mechanism by which they may opt-out of having their Personal Information shared with third-parties. We have elected the second option and you may request that your Personal Information not be shared with third-parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: Directory of Schools LLC, 73, St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED?**

The non-personally identifiable information that We collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If you elect to provide Us with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Us and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other sales and marketing efforts.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We partner with other third parties to provide specific services (e.g., student loans, text books, and other education-related products and services). When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. Service provider forms may ask for contact information (such as name, email, address) and sensitive information (such as date of birth and social security number) for in order to perform their service (such as to verify previous student loans). These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**WHAT IS THE UNSUBSCRIBE PROCESS?**

**Directoryofschools.com Offers:**

We use your email address to notify you of program updates, special offers and promotions. You may select at any time to opt-out of receiving emailed marketing offers from Us, Our partners and/or Our affiliated companies using the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom any future email you receive from Us.

**Non-affiliated 3rd Parties:**

If you prefer not to receive email offers from Our non-affiliated third-parties, you may click the "Unsubscribe" link available on the bottom of each email you receive from a non-affiliated third-party, and follow the instructions on the screen.

Please note that suppressed contact information will not be used for any other purpose other than to ensure compliance with your opt-out request, in response to inquiries by law enforcement and to comply with any other applicable state and/or federal laws regarding your choices for commercial email marketing, such as the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM).

**WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW DO WE USE THEM?**

Directoryofschools.com uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to help save and retrieve passwords used on Directoryofschools.com and to save information on past activities and other preferences. That way, you don't have to re-enter information every time you visit Directoryofschools.com.

When you visit Directoryofschools.com, we read the cookie to help target and personalize offers to you. For example, the cookie can help ensure that you don't see an offer that you have already completed. Cookies also let Directoryofschools.com know if We have repeat visitors.

We also use cookies to identify which sites 0ur repeat visitors are coming from. Directoryofschools.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. Directoryofschools.com respects your privacy and Directoryofschools.com cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Directoryofschools.com works with third-parties to serve ads on Our websites. These ads may contain cookies and/or action tags (also known as single pixel gifs) to measure advertising effectiveness and gather completely anonymous information. We have no access to or control over these cookies or action tags.

You are always free to decline these cookies if your browser permits, however, you may not be able to use certain features on Directoryofschools.com and you may be asked to re-enter your password more frequently during your session.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Directoryofschools.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and offline.

DO THESE SAME PRIVACY POLICIES APPLY TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES THAT YOU ACCESS THROUGH DIRECTORYOFSCHOOLS.COM?

No. The Privacy Policy appearing on Directoryofschools.com relates only to Directoryofschools.com. You will notice that Our website may contain links to other sites, such as Our partners. We cannot be responsible for the privacy and security practices of other websites that you may access through Directoryofschools.com, even if displayed within a frame on Our site. You should always review a particular site's privacy and security policies when linking to that site before revealing any personal information to that site.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to obtain changes to this Privacy Policy electronically by visiting this Site. We require you to check back from time to time to review changes to Our Privacy Policy.

**TRANSFERABILITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

In the event We go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of Our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by means of notice on [Our Sites] for thirty (30) days prior to any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Information. For more information, please refer to the section labeled "Privacy Policy Changes," above.

**A SPECIAL NOTE REGARDING PEOPLE UNDER THE AGE OF 18 YEARS OLD**

Consumers under the age of 18 must not send any personal information to Us-including but not limited to their name, address or email address. Further, We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information from any individual under the age of 13. Our intention is to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). If a parent or guardian has knowledge or is made aware a child under the age of 13 has provided Us with Personal Information through Our site, Contact Us and We will delete the information about the child from Our database.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about the practices of the Directoryofschools.com you can contact Us by visiting the Contact Us section of this website, or via postal mail at: Directory of Schools LLC, 73, St. James Drive, Santa Rosa, CA 95403.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE (PRIVACY POLIC1INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES0. YOU AGREE THAT THE OUR LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY US TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.
